<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="app_name">Android Guide</string>
    <string name="terms">Terminology</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <color name="red">#bb3737</color>
    <color name="yellow">#ffff66</color>
    <string name="aboutString">James Boyer - Computer Programming and Analysis</string>
    <string name="helpStringMain">Terminology: will allow you to search for android related terms.\n
       Website: will allow you to view a collection of sites related to android development</string>
    <string name="helpStringTerms">After three letters you will be suggested android terms,
                                   click to see their definitions</string>
    <string name="helpStringWebsite">This list of android development websites will help you
                                     with development. click to open the links</string>
    <string name="websites">Websites</string>
    <string name="web_instr">Browse the links below for helpful information about android development</string>
    <string name="term_instr">Start searching for android terms in the textbox below</string>
    <string-array
        name="list_urls">
        <item>Googles android development site</item>
        <item>Popular android development forum</item>
        <item>List of specific android tutorials-Vogella</item>
        <item>MIT\'s app development guide</item>
        <item>Android open source development guide</item>
        <item>Learning to use the action bar</item>
        <item>Parsing XML data in android</item>
        <item>Android blog</item>
        <item>Weekly android newsletter</item>
        <item>Android backend server tutorials</item>
        <item>Simple guide for new android developers</item>
        <item>Icon generators</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="list_urls_links">
        <item>https://developer.android.com/training/index.html</item>
        <item>http://forum.xda-developers.com/</item>
        <item>http://www.vogella.com/tutorials/android.html</item>
        <item>http://appinventor.mit.edu/explore/</item>
        <item>http://source.android.com/source/developing.html</item>
        <item>http://www.sitepoint.com/better-user-interfaces-android-action-bar/</item>
        <item>http://www.sitepoint.com/learning-to-parse-xml-data-in-your-android-app/</item>
        <item>http://www.smashingmagazine.com/tag/android/</item>
        <item>http://androidweekly.net/</item>
        <item>https://parse.com/docs/android_guide</item>
        <item>http://www.techrepublic.com/blog/software-engineer/a-newbies-guide-to-android-development/</item>
        <item>http://romannurik.github.io/AndroidAssetStudio/</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array
        name="list_terms">
        <item>ADB</item>
        <item>Emulator</item>
        <item>Android</item>
        <item>Screenshot2</item>
        <item>Gradle</item>
        <item>lint</item>
        <item>Project</item>
        <item>Panel</item>
        <item>Toolbar</item>
        <item>Status Bar</item>
        <item>Preview pane</item>
        <item>Android pane</item>
        <item>Project explorer</item>
        <item>idea folder</item>
        <item>Intellisense</item>
        <item>Modules</item>
        <item>Live layout</item>
        <item>git init</item>
        <item>git commit</item>
        <item>git push</item>
        <item>git add</item>
        <item>git pull</item>
        <item>git branch</item>
        <item>git clone</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="list_terms_def">
        <item>The android debug bridge, it essentially provides a bridge to the
  android device. It has various features that involve interacting with
  the current android device. We used it to install our apk file via
  \'adb install path/to/apk.apk\', this put our built android application
  onto the virtual device so we could test our app. We also used it to connect
  to the android virtual device  via \'adb shell\' this let us access the filesystem
  of the virtual device allowing us to view the filesystem and remove files.</item>

        <item>The emulator command allowed us to start the virtual devices via
  \'emulator -avd avdname\' emulator also allows us to change many aspects of
  the emulator such as debugging options, audio options, networking options,
  ui options and more. It is basically a way to start virtual devices and
  customize many aspects about them.</item>
        <item>The android command provides a way to list your current android virtual
  devices(\'android list avd\') and also create new ones(\'android create avd -n [name] -t [targetid]\')
  Also if you need to you can also move update and delete AVDs. It provides
  everything you need for managing your virtual devices.</item>
        <item>The screenshot2 command lets you take a snapshot of the current virtual device
  \'screenshot2 -e lab01.png\', \'-e\' specifies that you want to capture the first emulator.
  It is pretty simple and only has a couple more options including \'-d\' which captures
  the first android device, \'-s\' allows you to specify a serial number, and \'-l\' which captures
  the snapshot in landscape mode</item>
        <item>Gradle is a very important command, it builds your app. If you have a build.gradle file
  in your project directory and run \'gradle build\', assuming the app has no errors, it will
  create a huge build directory which includes your .apk file which is what is run on the
  android device.</item>
        <item>Lint allows for analysis of your source code and outputting it in a
  .xml(\'lint --xml [output.xml] [projectdir]\') or .html(\'lint --html [output.html] [projectdir]\')
  file. It reports errors and warnings about your source code clearly and also allowing for some
  customization of what errors are shown or not such as \'-w\' which ignores warnings and only looks
  for errors
</item>
        <item>A project is your whole project which contains everything required for your
   app to successfully build.</item>
        <item>A panel is a section that can provide information or tools that can be opened
   by clicking it.</item>
        <item>A toolbar is a list of shortcuts which allow you to open various things or
   preform tasks, it is also customizable allowing you to add or remove
   shortcuts.</item>
        <item>A status bar displays notifications about updates and information like the
   android studio version.</item>
        <item>The preview pane should show your android device and what the layout will
   currently look like, it also has various options to customize the preview
   device.</item>
        <item>The android pane has options to interact with your current running virtual
   device such as screenshots, recordings, log info and more. </item>
        <item>The project explorer allows you to view your source tree as a hierarchy and
   open files from there.</item>
        <item>The .idea folder stores many xml files which contain information
   about the project for example gradle settings, module settings version
   control settings and more.</item>
        <item>Intellisense will provide a list of valid completions to your code in order
   to speed up your coding process and help you keep track of valid keywords. </item>
        <item>modules make up a project, example a module contains the source code and app
   resources.</item>
        <item>Live layout is a preview of what your app layout will look on the screen and
   it changes as you code.</item>
        <item>git init will create an empty git repository.</item>
        <item>git commit will record and save any changes to the repository.</item>
        <item>git push will update your remote repository on github and your local
   repository.</item>
        <item>git add will add contents to your index.</item>
        <item>git pull will fetch contents from another repository and merge with your
   project.</item>
        <item>git branch will allow you list, create or delete branches.</item>
        <item>git clone will allow you to copy a repository into a new local directory.</item>

    </string-array>


</resources>
